Email Screen and Microtext
Good Morning
Upjam Good Morning
This is Takehara's Good Morning
Yoo-hoo!
Good morning
Got it
It's been a while since I've been up JAM
It's often a long time since I was at a staple festival or JAM It's been a long time since I was at a staple festival or JAM
Often a long time.
It's often used here, like during Staplerfest. Result announcement.
Yes, it is.
It's big.
For a moment, it looked sparkling already.
It was beautiful. It was sparkling.
Is the route okay? It's fine, BGM, it just doesn't have an aura yet. You're not in costume, you're not in makeup, you don't look like you're going to be the last one out.
It's not like I'm the last one to leave the show.
If you look at my eyebrows, they are cute.
I think it's going to go up after I put on the hat.
Raised?
A little bit to a nice length.
I drank half of it.
I got a really cute throat!
I'm so happy.
I'm sweating a little.
You sweated? That's...
You're not sweating?
I can't see it. I can't see it.
They say you can't see it.
You're sweating like a pig.
Tokimaro?
He was silent.
He said I'm cute.
He's cute.
He said you're cute.
I can't hear the audience, so I'm going to listen to the audio.
Okay, I'm going to go to the show.
I'm going to the show.
It doesn't look like that.
Well then, let's get you on the air right away! Please!
Here he comes!
Good morning.
We've been waiting for you.
Yes! Your heart
Rock on!
We are the Super Tokimeki Center.
We look forward to working with you.
Okay, next, Sakai, the first one.
Ah, this is Kitto-kun!
Aaaaah!
Did I make a mistake?
Next time, when you're thinking of a different girl...
Yes!
You're right!
I'm sorry!
Don't shoot!
No, I don't want to shoot! Don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot.
No, why don't you shoot me?
I don't know, I really know, like three-tenths and stuff.
I'm scared, it's not a parking party, already.
And, um, next year, we're doing a one-man show here in Yokoyari.
That's great. I'm going to do a one-man show.
I'd like to be allowed to do it. That's great.
So, what kind of person do you want to be at that time?
I hope I can give this kind of performance,
I think about it a lot,
I also think about my personal life,
I think about my personal life.
I see.
I am going to Indonesia. We all went to Indonesia this summer for a live concert,
Since Aki-chan wrote about it, I would like to tell you an episode,
Please do.
I stayed there for about 6 days and 5 nights,
I stayed in the same room with Aki-chan every day. That's how long I stayed there,
I stayed in the same room with Aki-chan every day.
Oh, really?
Yes, I did.
A new room.
That's right.
I think everyone knows that,
On the last day, it was early in the morning,
Aki-chan and the others decided to stay up until morning,
We had a sweets party,
We had a sweets party and talked about staying up until morning with the theme song. We were talking about having a candy party and staying up until morning with the theme song,
But then I noticed that Aki-chan was sleeping beside me,
Ha-ha-ha.
That's not like him.
That's right. So, I was sleepy too,
I said, "Let's go to sleep,
I fell asleep, and even though I fell asleep, I'm still sleeping,
I said, "Let's go to sleep," and that was just one word. That's it.
That's right, but I was waking Aki-chan up almost every day,
Would I be able to get up on the last day? We were talking about whether we would be able to get up on the last day,
We had two beds.
We had been sleeping separately.
Oh, really?
That's right.
But on the last day, Aki-chan was in my bed the whole time. Then we left together!
That's the best story ever!
In the last period.
We made love in bed.
How was it, Aki-chan? How was it? Why did you go into it?
I think we got to know each other better through Indonesia.
So I thought I wanted to spend a little more time with you.
Yay!
So cute!
So, what happened when you joined Hanayama?
At first, Aki-chan was sleeping,
I went out for a while and got out of bed,
When I came back, I felt Akichan's warmth,
Oh, my God!
I was so happy.
Ha-ha-ha.
How's it going? I should have recorded it. Yes, I was happy to feel the warmth of Indonesia! Ha-ha-ha!
I, uh... I, uh... I should have recorded it, but...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please don't spy on me!
I just want to keep it like this.
It's a happy summer memory.
That's nice. Then, since Aki-chan is also in Indonesia, may I ask you, Aki-chan, by the way?
Yes! I was also able to go to a live concert in Indonesia.
Everyone in Indonesia was really kind to me.
I was so grateful,
I had such a great time, but why don't you write "Indonesia" on your website?
Why?
It's like it's just the two of you.
Yeah, I don't know, they didn't put "Indonesia" in there, you know.
Caples comes for the fireworks, pure and simple.
The best part is, there's six of us,
A lot of topics, you guys don't want to hear about it.
No, no, no, it's fine.
You've done a lot of good. You know, right now.
I was feeling very desperate.
We will be back here in Yokohama Arena next January,
That's it, isn't it?
That's right.
What should we do? Really, the chap is pretty egregious about it.
So, if, or rather, if, for sure, next year on January 27 and 28, Yokohama Arena,
I'm working hard to fill it up this time.
Oh, wow.
Applause.
That's a good feeling. Really, really.
It's hot.
I kind of want to do this as an appeal to adults.
I'd like to do this with them in a side bath, something like that.
But there's one thing I can't tell you yet.
I can't tell you yet.
I'm waiting for the best performance.
Oh, no!
There's an idiot, I didn't do it.
I didn't do it.
This is something that only those who come will understand.
I really hope you experience that!
It's nice.
I'm looking forward to it.
I like it.
Let's go!
Don!
Please let us know about future announcements.
Yes! We will be releasing a new single, Kawaii Memoriado, on the 27th of May.
We will be releasing a new single, "Kawaii Memoriado" on the 27th of May.
Please look forward to it.
And as I mentioned earlier,
Next year, on January 27 and 28, 2024, we will be performing here at Yokohama Arena.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
We have a lot of teak on sale now, so please come and visit us. We are waiting for you.
We are waiting for you.
Also, Jam Jam Jam, from now on.
We're going to start the live performance of the arms room battle.
It's going to be sparkling.
Your eyes will be dazzling.
Yay!
Yeah!
Balls! Another ball!
That's why there's two of them.
Thanks for the togetherness.
Thanks to all of you.
And at the end of the day, we were all united again! Thank you so much!
That's all! This is Yavan, the top youtube promoter! Thank you very much! That's all for Top Heavy 2010 Yabang! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much! It's over! Thank you! Thank you for your hard work! Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work! The third member is in row 3, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6!
We are the M for "Kikimeki Center".
We are M, the center of M. Best regards.
Kyun February!
February is also a good month for us.
Please give my regards to you.
Wow, you're so real.
Kyun already!
I want to shoot an animation.
What? You're filming?
I'm so excited!
Parker?
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Okay, excuse me.
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
Idol, you're cute.
Miri-san.
I know her.
Someone I know.
Cheese. Cheese. It's someone who knows.
It's an at-jam today. It's an at-jam.
I'm feeling summer because it's a festival,
I haven't felt the heat on stage yet,
That's why I'm excited to keep going for a few more minutes.
And it's here in Yokohai.
It's where we're going to be alone.
So I hope I can see the atmosphere of what it will be like again,
I never thought I would be able to come to a hat jam like I can do a triathlon! I was like, "I can't believe you're coming!
I didn't come to this event, and there are so many idols here, but I really wanted to be a part of this event,
I was like, "What? I thought, "Is it OK?
So, I will do my best to give a performance that will make you think "Otogi".
I will do my best.
I'm a bird, after all.
Gao is the bird.
It's a special kind of immediate power, or power.
But I think the best point is to perform as if it were a special product,
I'm greedy, and I'm looking forward to it. Back to back. There are various idols here at the festival,
With so many people gathered like this,
As long as I locate and incorporate all of those people, I'm free.
That's right.
I'm going to be able to afford to be a side.
Oh no.
I'm not losing sleep yet,
I'm not losing any sleep yet.
Applause!
From all of us.
Let's do it.
Let's do it
Hey, when you get a hold of yourself
Let's do it.
Are you feeling better?
No, I didn't sleep at the last show.
I missed you already.
Sorry, it's not a sad memory.
Your first show back?
I made a big deal out of it,
I really wanted to go to the show so badly,
Today is my first live performance in a long time,
Please enjoy the show.
I will do my best.
I saw the video.
I heard rumors.
The fans tell me about it.
What did you say, Aki-chan? They told me.
I'm still crying.
I'm crying now.
And I'm crying.
I'm sorry... for bringing up such sad memories.
I'm so sorry.
Aki-chan asked me if I love you, Hiyo-chan. You asked me if I love Hiyo-chan.
You asked me if I love you, right? Yes, I do. Oh, my God. Thank you.
Did she say she loved you?
But I made her listen. At home.
Did you get it?
He said he loved it, so I was very careful.
Yes!
I had to ask.
I also received a sneeze.
And sneeze, too, kishakishakishan.
Yes, three times.
He already said it was great.
Good.
My soul is telling me,
I guess so.
And then there are those who are not like this.
People who are watching on TV.
We can deliver it to them, too.
We can send a message to them that this is a special selection,
I hope you are doing your best,
I will do my best!
I'll definitely do my best,
I don't mean that I could see the advertisement of the Special Selection,
There are many fans out there. So, this is a great chance for you to reach Yokohama Arena next year!
We will lock on to the hearts of many and never let them go!
I will do my best!
I will definitely take you to Yokohama Arena!
I'll do my best!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'll do my best! I'll do my best! I'm looking forward to it! Fun~ Let's go for it!
Early!
Quick!
Use it!
Dumpster, dumpster!
Oh, you're making me nervous.
Please!
I'll do my best! Run along that way.
Those good old days...
I wonder if I'll be able to hold on or if I'll be shaken
I'm so moved that I'm going to cry when I think about doing it here next year. I'm so excited!
It's so big! Wow! It's so big!
So big!
Let's have fun!
One time! Lightly! Let's have fun! Let's have fun! Koizumi, Mirina, Hisaka, Haruka, Oki, Miyasu, Nagata, Chie,
Rakuhan!
Let's go for it.
I'm going.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thanks for your hard work.
Here we go.
Oh, there it is.
Let's go.
I've already been there.
Me too.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Please. Are you okay? Yeah, I'm fine.
Inside, Daddy loves you too.
Inside, I just love Kanamine!
I feel like I'm going inside.
All right.
Here we go.
I'm not nervous.
Let's go hand in hand, hand in hand.
Hello, hello, ohkun. Okay, I'm going to start. Please do. Happy sensitivity.
I'm off. I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much
I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much.
Look at me. I want you. I want your face too.
I'm a junior high school girl. Don't say anything.
You can sing if you want.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no...
Thank you. By all means, psychopath.
Congratulations on realizing you really like it. Once again, the next one follows.
See you again.
Have fun.
Congratulations.
See you again here again.
We'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much for your patience.
Thank you very much.
He's so cute.
It's amazing.
You're surprisingly beautiful.
I love the camera.
I just took this out.
I didn't know if I was in the right frame.
Yes, I see it.
I'll talk.
I can't stop the sweat in my nose.
It's so wide.
I knew it! Walking on the side.
I was so nervous at first.
I was so nervous at first. When I got out. I was nervous at first.
I was so nervous before I went out, it was terrible. But as I got into it, I started to get a grasp of it,
I was really nervous at first,
I was really nervous at first.
It took me a while to catch on,
But it was a lot of fun.
We rehearsed about 100 times,
I started about 3 months before the show.
It's hard to get a sense of it, isn't it?
Yes, I have a lot of confidence. You have to be confident.
But I'm sure it will be fun.
I was able to do a lot of different things because of the size of the place, and I had a lot of fun skiing at the end.
But I was also reminded that I need to work even harder.
I will do my best.
It was fun.
I'll be back in about 5 months or so with an update.
Oh no, five months from now!
I'm so excited!
No matter how many times I stand on this stage, it's still big.
No matter how many times I stand on this stage, it's still big. This stage is really big. I feel nervous no matter how many times I stand on it.
That's why I thought "Yokoyobyobi" was amazing.
I can stand there for two days in a row.
I want to improve my physical strength.
It took me a little time to get used to the stage today,
I want to get a good grasp of it before I get up on stage.
But the scan was great, wasn't it?
I felt like everyone wanted to be there.
The endless and stuff were really exciting.
It was good.
It was fun.
I'll work harder!
I'll do my best!
Yes, I'll do my best! At Jam is over.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
I knew it, the side bath, it was so big,
I cleaned it up so much.
I was surprised. I've had them dance a few times,
I don't remember it being this big.
I think so every time.
And this time, I was able to do the trick on the 5th day of Natodan! I'm a little nervous,
I'm a little nervous.
I was pretty nervous before the show started.
My heart was racing. My heart was racing. But Hito and Hiyori sang a song for me to turn on the heart throb switch,
I couldn't give them the guidance, but I was able to do my best.
Everyone got really excited,
I think there were many people who didn't know us,
I know there were a lot of people who didn't know us, but they were willing to get excited with us no matter what song we played,
The audience was also united in the last moon,
It was a lot of fun to do.
It was fun.
There were many idols on both sides of the stage,
I was happy when they came to see me.
I was also happy when they danced. There were also people on the lower side and the upper side of the stage. I was happy when they came to see me.
And if they danced, too,
It made me happy.
You were also at Shimote Kamite, weren't you?
Yes.
Not at all.
I was happy.
I was very happy.
We will be back on January 27th and 28th,
We will be back again on January 27th and 28th for our one-man show at the arena over there,
So, for those of you who are watching this channel today,
If you are watching this channel today, or if you are interested in us after watching the at jam, please come and see us at the Yokohama Arena,
If you are watching this channel today, or if you are interested in us after watching the at jam, please come and visit us at Yokohama Arena.
We look forward to seeing you there.
And we will do our best to perform at Jam again.
We want to do it again!
Again!
I'll do my best tomorrow!
Yes, I will do my best!
Thank you very much.
See you soon, I still have an unknown landscape in front of me, come on, let's go wherever you want.
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turned color
Paint a piece of the future on the canvas of my damaged heart
Blotting me out.
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
And when it's raining, I'll smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Good bye, good bye, to the me of yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools and rainbow puddles
I play the rainbow piano
Good bye, good bye, to me yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, I scare away the clouds of tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress Lalala...
Lalala... you